Guide to the Arthur E. Scott photograph collection, 1910-1976
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: People, 1910-1976; (Boxes 1-7, 12-22, 26-27, 29-42)
  - Subseries 1.4: Notable political figures, U.S. Supreme Court Justices and Foreign Dignitaires, 1921-1971
    - MacDonald, Ramsey, 1929-1933 (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; includes Herbert C. Hoover
    - Mitchell, William (Billy), 1910s-1920s (Box 27)
      5 glass plate negatives
    - Stone, Harlan F., 1930s (Box 27)
    - U.S. Supreme Court Justices, 1920s (Box 27)
    - Taft, William Howard, 1921-1930 (Box 27)
  - Subseries 1.5: Celebrities, 1923-1965
    Subseries 1.5 contains photographs of celebrities who visited Washington, D.C. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by name and then chronologically within each name.
    - Shepard, Alan, 1960s (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Astronauts, 1959-1962 (Box 21)
    - Brian, Mary, 1939 (Box 21)
    - Burr, Raymond, June 22, 1959 (Box 21)
    - Carey, Harry, March 24, 1940 (Box 21)
      2 negatives; with John Garfield
    - Cochran, Steve, 1937-1938 (Box 21)
      27 negatives
    - Coconut Grove night club, 1930s (Box 21)
      4 negatives; includes Carl Mainfort, Doris Stauffer, Bob Brockhurst, Irene Bordoni
    - Cooper, Gordon, September 14, 1965 (Box 21)
      6 negatives; with Charles Conrad, Jr., Hubert H. Humphrey, Jr.
    - Culpepper, Shirly, March 1955 (Box 21)
    - Dudley, Doris, March 31, 1940 (Box 21)
    - Evans, Dale, March 12, 1959 (Box 21)
      1 negative; with daughter
    - Glenn, John, 1959-1962 (Box 21)
      18 negatives; with Senators
    - Grissom, Gus, 1965 (Box 21)
      18 negatives; with John Young
    - Hannigan, Maie, 1920s-1930s (Box 21)
    - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr. (Mrs.), 1930s (Box 21)
      2 negatives; at French Embassy reception, with William McCracken and Martha Roundtree.
    - Jean, Gloria, 1940s (Box 21)
      14 negatives; with Bernie Kriesler and Hardie Meakin III
    - Mclean, Evelyn Walsh, 1933-1939 (Box 21)
    - O'Brien, Pat, December 19, 1939 (Box 21)
      1 negative; with James Farley
    - Reed, Macon, 1930s (Box 21)
      1 negative; at French Embassy party
    - Schirra, Wally, May 28, 1959 (Box 21)
      2 negatives; with Clifford P. Case
    - Shepard, Alan, 1959-1961 (Box 21)
      18 negatives; with John Glenn, Styles Bridges, Francis Case, Michael J. Mansfield, Norris H. Cotton, Prescott S. Bush
    - Thielfall, Paul, 1950s (Box 21)
    - Yates Sisters, Jerry, Carol, and Lynn, 1940s (Box 21)
    - Bremen Flyers, 1923-1929 (Box 27)
      2 glass plate negatives; includes Calvin Coolidge
    - Cohan, George M., 1929-1933 (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; includes Herbert C. Hoover, Sol Bloom
    - Del Rio, Dolores, July 17, 1929 (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; includes Charles Curtis
    - Gibbons, Floyd, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
  - Subseries 1.6: General, 1927-1975
    Subseries 1.6 is contains people who do not fit in other subseries, including politicians' families without the politician in the picture. This subseries is sorted alphabetically by name.
    - Carpenter, Liz, February 7, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      With children
    - Dupont, Pierre S., 1920s (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Duplicates of broken negatives
    - Ladies of the Senate, April 22, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Luncheon given for Betty Ford
    - Kid Pictures with Senators, 1960s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - McCubbin, M. D., June 25,1938 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Misc. People, 1930s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sinnott, Joseph J., 1910s (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Balzo, MaryJane del, 1930s-1940s (Box 21)
    - Bellmon, Shirley, 1970s (Box 21)
    - Boyd, Ben, 1920s (Box 21)
    - Boyd, Maryann, 1930s (Box 21)
    - Brobeck, George K., 1930s (Box 21)
    - Burdick, Quentin, Staffers, 1965-1967 (Box 21)
    - Burger, George, 1950s-1960s (Box 21)
      28 negatives
    - Carpenter, Liz, February 7, 1953 (Box 21)
      6 negatives; with children
    - Clary, [Alla], 1940s-1950s (Box 21)
    - D'Augustino, Carmen, 1930s-1940s (Box 21)
    - Dulles, Allen, 1950s (Box 21)
    - Eisenhower, Mamie, 1950s (Box 22)
    - Garner, Mariette Rheiner, 1930s (Box 22)
    - Federal Housing Authority group, September 18, 1958 (Box 22)
    - Forbes, Malcolm, July 11, 1957 (Box 22)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, Office Staff, 1940s-1950s (Box 22)
    - Funderburk, J. Baxter, October 25 ,1957 (Box 22)
    - Glaser, Myron, December 28, 1958 (Box 22)
      3 negatives; Christmas party
    - Goldwater, Margaret, January 27, 1956 (Box 22)
    - GOP Kitchen Kabinet, 1950s (Box 22)
    - Hammann, Reid L., 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - Harrison Bible Class, St. Luke's Methodist Church, 1959-1962 (Box 22)
    - Hatch, Elaine, 1950s (Box 22)
    - Hawaiian Youth, 1960s (Box 22)
    - Hoover, Lou Henry, 1929-1933 (Box 22)
      1 negative; at Red Cross
    - House Page Boys, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - Immaculate High School student, June 2, 1960 (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Claudia Taylor (Lady Bird), 1961-1965 (Box 22)
    - Johnson, Victor, 1940s-1950s (Box 22)
      1 negative; with A. B. Herman and Lee Potter
    - Kansas farm group, 1930s-1940s (Box 22)
    - Kentucky State Society, April 24, 1959 (Box 22)
    - Lee, Eleanor, 1940s-1950s (Box 22)
    - Legion of Valor, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - Lewis, John L., 1950s (Box 22)
    - Maragon, John, 1930s-1940s (Box 22)
      1 negative; with his wife
    - McMiller, Ralph, July 30, 1963 (Box 22)
    - Mooney, [?], October 15, 1959 (Box 22)
      2 negatives; coal industry
    - New Mexico State Society, 1940s-1950s (Box 22)
    - Nixon Family, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - Reilly, James D., 1950s (Box 22)
      1 negative; copy of portrait in a publication
    - Sanborn, Herbert, September 1, 1959 (Box 22)
    - Sanborn, Katherine Joanne, June 2, 1960 (Box 22)
      13 negatives; daughter of Kimball Sanborn
    - St. Matthews Church group, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - Scott, Arthur E., 1930s (Box 22)
      1 negative; with F. I. Thompson
    - Swick, Craig, January 18-19, 1962 (Box 22)
    - Townsend, Franic, 1930s (Box 22)
    - Tudin, Kitchie, April 18, 1958 (Box 22)
    - Tufts College Chorus, February 5, 1960 (Box 22)
      2 negatives; with Professor K. MacKillop
    - Unidentified people, 1930s-1960s (Box 22)
    - West, Hugh A., January 16, 1960 (Box 22)
      15 negatives; with his wife
    - WFMD radio station, 1930s-1940s (Box 22)
      9 negatives; with American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers
    - Williams, Clare, 1950s (Box 22)
      2 negatives; with Victoria Hruska
    - Wisconsin AAA, May 8, 1959 (Box 22)
    - Wrigley, Tom, Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks, February 21, 1951 (Box 22)
    - Woodson Highschool orchestra students, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), January 10, 1961 (Box 22)
    - Coolidge, John, December 23, 1927 (Box 27)
    - Dupont, Pierre S., 1920s (Box 27)
      2 glass plate negatives; see duplicate prints in folder 7.2
    - Gann, Dolly, 1929-1933 (Box 27)
    - Hoover, Lou Henry, 1930-1931 (Box 27)
      6 glass plate negatives
    - General people, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Includes White House photographers, Bess and Mary Margaret Truman
    - Scott, Arthur E., personal photos, 1950s (Box 37)
      Large format color slides
    - Scott, Arthur E., personal photos, 1950s-1960s (Box 41)
- Series 2: Places, 1927-1976; (Boxes 7-9, 22-23, 27, 31, 43)
  This series contains photographs of Washington, D.C. and the surrounding area, as well as other national and over seas locations. These places includes buildings, parks, landmarks, and monuments. This series is divided into the following subseries:
  - Subseries 2.1: U.S. Capitol Building, 1956-1976
    Subseries 2.1 contains photographs of the U.S. Captiol building, interior and exterior.
    - U.S. Capitol Building, 1930s-1970s (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Cleaning chandelier at the U.S. Capitol building, August 4, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Flag raising over the U.S. Capitol Building, June 14, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Includes Carolyn Hartman, Wes Holden, Barry M. Goldwater
    - Prayer Room, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Rotunda Images, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Includes Senators (maybe John F. Kennedy inauguration)
    - Statuary Hall, 1960s (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Capitol building, 1950s-1970s (Box 22)
      35 negatives; includes Senate Subway
    - U.S. Capitol Building, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
      12 glass plate negatives
  - Subseries 2.2: Washington, D.C. Area, 1927-1964
    Subseries 2.2 contains photographs of the Washington, D.C. area, including parks, landmarks, monuments, and other buildings. These photographs are arranged alphabetically by location name.
    - Aerial Pictures of Washington, D.C., 1930s (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge, January 17, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Arlington National Cemetery Amphitheater, 1940s (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Boating Scenes, Washington, D.C., 1930s (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Jail and Morgue, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower Executive Office Buidling (formerly State, War, and Navy Building), 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Embassy of Japan, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Embassy of Mexico, mural, November 25, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Embassy of Russia, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Federal Triangle Complex, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Interior of Washington, D.C. building, War Department?, 1920s (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Jimmy LaFontaine's Gambling House, 1920s-1930s (Box 8, Folder 12)
      Located at Bladensburg Rd. and Eastern Ave.
    - Library of Congress, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Lincoln Memorial, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Meridian Park, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 15)
      16th and Florida Ave, NW
    - Misc. Washington, D.C. Area, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Mount Vernon, Virginia, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - National Archives, Interior, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Washington National Cathedral, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - National Geographic Building, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Pan American Union Building, Interior, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Patterson House, Dupont Circle, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      Temporary home for Calvin Coolidge while White House was getting a new roof
    - Potomac River, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 23)
      Includes President's Cup Regatta, Great Falls
    - Russell Senate Office Building, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Shoreham Building, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 25)
      15th and H St., NW
    - Smithsonian Arts and Industries Building, November 9, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Standard Oil Co. of New Jersey building, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, Arlington National Cemetery, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 28)
      Includes religious statue
    - Union Station, 1920s-1930s (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - U.S. Soldier's Home, Scott Building, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 30)
      Now called Sherman Building
    - US Treasury, vault, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Vice President's Office, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Washington Circle, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Washington Monument, 1930s (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - White House, 1930s-1940s (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - 108 4th St., SE, 1930s-1940s (Box 22)
    - 403-405-407 2nd St., SE, September 25, 1964 (Box 22)
    - 2760 32nd St., NW, Septebember 11, 1956 (Box 22)
    - 3415 Volta Place, NW, October 27, 1959 (Box 22)
      3 negatives; home of Alexander Graham Bell's servants; with Dorothy Walker Bush
    - 4608 Reservoir Rd., 1960s (Box 22)
    - 5020 Lowell St. NW, October 15, 1956 (Box 22)
    - Blan House, 1950s (Box 22)
    - National Zoo, 1950s (Box 22)
    - Pentagon Cafeteria, 1950s (Box 22)
    - Sears Department Store, April 5, 1959 (Box 22)
    - Unidentifed houses, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
    - White House, 1950s-1960s (Box 22)
      22 negatives; includes color positives
    - Arlington National Cemetery, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
    - Barbara Fritchie House, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
    - Friends Church, 13th and Irving Sts., NW, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; Herbert C. Hoover's church
    - Northeast corner, 6th and Pennsylvania Ave., NW, June 9, 1932 (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; National Guard Armory
    - Northeast corner, 14th and Pennsylvania Ave., NW, June 9, 1932 (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; buildings razed
    - Northwest corner, 3rd and Pennsylvania Ave., NW, June 9, 1932 (Box 27)
      2 glass plate negatives; buildings razed
    - Taft, William Howard, Home, 1920s (Box 27)
    - Union Station, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
      1 glass plate negative; statue of an American Indian killing a buffalo
    - Washington D.C., general, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
    - Washington Hotel, Northeast Corner of 15th and Pennsylvania Ave., NW, June 9, 1932 (Box 27)
    - White House, 1920s-1930s (Box 27)
      4 glass plate negatives
  - Subseries 2.3: U.S. Supreme Court Building, 1930s-1940s
    Subseries 2.3 contains photographs of the U.S. Supreme Court Building, interior and exterior, including construction of the building.
    - U.S. Supreme Court Building, 1930s-1940s (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Supreme Court Building, 1930s-1940s (Box 22)
      7 negatives; includes construction
  - Subseries 2.4: National and International, 1930s-1958
    Subseries 2.4 contains photographs of national and international locations, including the Panama Canal Zone.
    - Tampa Nugget cigar factory, Florida, 1930s-1940s (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Far East, June 25, 1958 (Box 23)
      3 negatives; "health pictures"
    - Puerto Rico, 1960s (Box 23)
    - Rome, Italy and Vatican City, 1960s-1970s (Box 31)
      commerical tourist slides
    - Panama Canal Zone, 1940s-1950s (Box 43)
      mounted aerial photographs
    - Panama Canal Zone, 1940s-1950s (Box Oversize)
- Series 3: Events, 1921-1976; (Boxes 9-11, 23-25, 27, 30, 33, 35-36, 38-42)
  This series contains photographs of events such as natural disaster, theater performances, dinners, meetings, speeches, press conferences, campaigns, conventions, inaugurations, and the presentation of Buddy Poppies. Figures included in these photographs include Congresspeople, Presidents, and other politicians. This series is divided into the following subseries:
  - Subseries 3.1: Natural disasters, 1930s
    Subseries 3.1 contains photographs of the aftermath of natural disasters.
    - Flooded roadway between Norfolk and Virginia Beach, 1930s (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Norfolk, Virginia
    - Fireman killed in wreck of hook and ladder engine, 1930s (Box 23)
      1 negative; Baltimore, Maryland
    - Harper's Ferry, West Virginia flood, 1930s (Box 23)
      1 negative; highway bridge washed out in flood
    - Flooded roadway between Norfolk and Virginia Beach, 1930s (Box 23)
      2 negatives; Norfolk, Virginia
  - Subseries 3.2: Dinners, Meetings, and Fundraisers, 1932-1968
    Subseries 3.2 contains photographs of dinners, meetings, and fundraisers.
    - Administrative Assistants Luncheon, July 28, 1955 (Box 23)
    - Conference on Immigration, January 13, 1964 (Box 23)
      9 negatives; includes Lyndon B. Johnson, James Eastland, Phillip A. Hart, Hiram L. Fong
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., birthday breakfast, October 14, 1958 (Box 23)
      20 negatives; Dwight and Mamie Eisenhower attend birthday party at Statler Hotel
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. and Richard M. Nixon, dinner, January 5, 1961 (Box 23)
      30 negatives; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower, Richard M. Nixon, Republican Senators
    - East Texas Chamber of Commerce lunch, 1939 (Box 23)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., lunch, October 14, 1966 (Box 23)
      14 negatives; includes British Foreign Secretary George Brown, Margaret Chase Smith, Maurine Neuberger
    - Lincoln Day $5.00 Dinner, Febrary 8, 1956 (Box 23)
    - Morton, Thruston, dinner, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
      4 negatives; includes Everett M. Dirksen, Thruston Morton
    - Murphy, George, luncheon, July 1964 (Box 23)
      11 negatives; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower, William Miller, Walt Disney, John Eisenhower, Len Hall, Thruston Morton, Richard M. Nixon, Barry M. Goldwater, George Murphy
    - Nixon, Richard M., coffee meeting, July 18, 1968 (Box 23)
      30 negatives; inclues Richard M. Nixon and Republican Senators
    - Policy Luncheon 1965, September 14, 1965 (Box 23)
      6 negatives; includes Richard M. Nixon, Everett M. Dirksen, John G. Tower, Leonard B. Jordan, Gordon L. Allott
    - Policy Luncheon 1966, August 23, 1966 (Box 23)
      12 negatives; includes Richard M. Nixon, John G. Tower, Lee Hruska, Edward W. Brooke, III, Everett M. Dirksen, Milton Young, Bourke B. Hickenlooper, Paul J. Fannin, Leverett Saltonstall
    - Potter, Charlie, party, April 15, 1962 (Box 23)
      23 negatives
    - Republican Party Chairman reception, April 16, 1956 (Box 23)
    - Republican Party dinner for Dwight D. Eisenhower and Richard M. Nixon, April 17, 1956 (Box 23)
      4 negatives; promoting "Ring the Bells and Tell the People" slogan
    - Republican Party dinner at Sheraton Park Hotel, June 8, 1959 (Box 23)
      20 negatives; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower
    - Republican Party breakfast, July 29, 1955 (Box 23)
      3 negatives; includes George Bender, Dwight D. Eisenhower
    - Republican Senators dinner, February 18, 1957 (Box 23)
      1 negative; includes Frederick Payne, Everett M. Dirksen, Wallace F. Bennett, Prescott S. Bush
    - Republican Senators dinner, August 24, 1960 (Box 23)
      34 negatives; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower, Richard M. Nixon, Republican Senators
    - Veterans Dinner, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
    - Washington, D.C. Press Club Barbecue, May 21, 1932 (Box 27)
  - Subseries 3.3: Bill signings, Speeches, and Press Conferences, 1937-1974
    Subseries 3.3 contains photographs of bill signings, speeches, and press conferences.
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., State of the Union, August 12, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 80th Congress, 1947 (Box 23)
      3 negatives; swearing in House Officers
    - 82nd Congress, January 3, 1951 (Box 23)
      1 negatives; includes Samuel Rayburn, Adolph Sabath
    - Automation bill, August 19, 1964 (Box 23)
      9 negatives; includes Lyndon B. Johnson, Hiram L. Fong, Jacob K. Javits, Joseph Clark, Jennings Randolph, Bob Bartlett, Philip Hart
    - Civil Rights Act, July 1964 (Box 23)
      1 negatives; photograph of a shadow box containg a pen and a photograph of Lyndon B. Johnson handing a pen to Everett M. Dirksen
    - Federal Airport Act SII53, March 11, 1964 (Box 23)
      1 negative; includes Lyndon B. Johnson
    - Hawaii statehood, August 21, 1959 (Box 23)
      11 negatives; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower, Richard M. Nixon,Oren Long, Hiram L. Fong, Samuel Rayburn, Daniel Inouye
    - House Naval Affairs Committee, 1930s-1940s (Box 23)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., bill signing, July 20, 1965 (Box 23)
      1 negatives; includes John G. Tower
    - Miscellaneous Congress Openings, 1950s-1960s (Box 23)
      24 negatives
    - Pay-raise bill, August 14, 1964 (Box 23)
      10 negatives; includes Lyndon B. Johnson, Hiram L. Fong, Frank Carlson, J. Calib Boggs
    - Policy Luncheon press conference, September 14, 1965 (Box 23)
      3 negatives; includes Richard M. Nixon
    - Radio gallery, 1939 (Box 23)
      1 negative; includes Fulton Lewis, William Bankhead, William Barbour, John Dempsey
    - Republican National Committee meeting, July 25-30, 1960 (Box 23)
      14 negatives; includes Richard M. Nixon
    - Senate Appropriations Subcommittee on Defense, February 4, 1960 (Box 23)
      3 negatives; includes Arleigh Burke
    - Special Session called by Franklin D. Roosevelt, November 15, 1937 (Box 23)
      5 negatives; includes William Bankhead
    - Veterans bill, December 6, 1973 (Box 23)
      4 negatives; includes Richard M. Nixon, Strom Thurmond, Clifford P. Hansen, Rupert V. Hartke
  - Subseries 3.4: Campaigns and Conventions, 1952-1974
    Subseries 3.4 contains photographs of campaigns and conventions, mainly consisting of events for members of the Republican Party.
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., Ronald W. Reagan, and Richard M. Nixon at Republican National Convention, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Nixon, Richard M., addresses joint session of Congress, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Nixon, Richard M., addresses joint session of Congress, 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 1952 election, Cherrydale, VA (Box 23)
    - 1956 Republican National Headquarters (Box 23)
    - 1960 Republican National Convention, July 25-30, 1960 (Box 23)
      7 negatives; includes Dwight D. Eisenhower
    - 1960 Republican National Convention, general views, July 25-30, 1960 (Box 24)
    - 1960 Republican National Convention, Richard M. Nixon, Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr., July 25-30, 1960 (Box 24)
    - 1960 Republican National Convention, Nelson A. Rockefeller, July 25-30, 1960 (Box 24)
    - 1960 Republican National Convention, Senators, July 25-30, 1960 (Box 24)
      13 negatives; includes Henry Dworshak, Hiram L. Fong, Andrew Schoeppel, Thruston Morton, Carl Curtis, Roman L. Hruska, John Cooper, Karl Mundt, Henry Styles Bridges, George D. Aiken, Milton Young, Bourke B. Hickenlooper
    - 1964 Republican National Convention, demonstrations, July 13-18, 1964 (Box 24)
      8 negatives; includes demonstrations for Margaret Chase Smith, William Scranton
    - 1964 Republican National Convention, Barry M. Goldwater, July 10-18, 1964 (Box 24)
      40 negatives; includes speeches and nomination
    - 1964 Republican National Convention, Senators and Reprsentatives, July 13-18, 1964 (Box 24)
      150 negatives; includes Leverett Saltonstall, Gordon L. Allott, John G. Tower, Clifford P. Case, John S.Cooper, William Miller, Roman L. Hruska, Thurston Morton, Bourke B. Hickenlooper, Leverett Saltonstall, Wallace F. Bennett, Peter H. Dominick, Milward L. Simpson, Jacob K. Javits, Hiram L. Fong, Margaret Chase Smith, George D. Aiken
    - Campaign - New Senators, Faces and Biographies, January 18, 1963 (Box 24)
    - Nixon, Richard M., campaining in Hawaii, Los Angeles, California, August 1960 (Box 24)
    - 1964 Republican National Convention, July 13-18, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Includes Republican Policy Committee Elephant
    - 1964 Republican National Convention, July 13-18, 1964 (Box 33)
      Color slides
    - Campaigns, 1960s-1970s (Box 35)
      Color slides; Barry M. Goldwater, Richard S. Schweiker, William Scott
    - Nixon, Richard M., campaining in Hawaii, Los Angeles, California, August 1960 (Box 36)
      35 mm negatives, some color
    - Nixon, Richard M., campaining in Hawaii, Los Angeles, California, August 1960 (Box 38)
    - Nixon, Richard M., campaining in Hawaii, Los Angeles, California, August 1960 (Box 39)
  - Subseries 3.5: Inaugurations, 1956-1974
    Subseries 3.5 contains photographs of inauguration ceremonies and events.
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., Inauguration, January 20, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., Oath of Office, December 6, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Photos by Mickey Stenko, house Republican Party photographer
    - Ford, Gerald R., Jr., Oath of Office, December 6, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Godwin, Mills E., Inauguration as Virginia Governor, January 12, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      See inauguration program in folder 11.20
    - Kennedy, John F., Inauguration, January 20, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Nixon, Richard M., Inauguration, January 20, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Oath of Office, December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Oath of Office, December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Oath of Office, December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Oath of Office, December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson A., Oath of Office, December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)